hey M little question for you how do you
think this suit would look on an
assistant fire okay the owner of alandr
came over here to yell at me but instead
I made him some sauce and he offered me
the job as head chef oh my God you just
ruined the thing I was practicing the
whole way home but I'm so
happy can you believe it I finally get
to run my own kitchen oh you've waited
so
[Music]
long hey hey B Qui question for you yeah
how do you think the suit would look on
an assistant buyer at
Bloomingdales I don't know totally on
her coloring
and you got the job you got the job why
didn't you tell
me oh it's going to be so great I'm
going to get to help decide what we sell
I'm going have an office with walls and
everything I'm going to have
walles okay is this the day of good news
or what I got us a job the wedding
reception
oh um B I kind of need to talk to you
about that
um well I I I I think it might be time
for me to take a step back from the
catering but we've only had one
job I know but now we have this second
one and it just it feels like it's
snowballing you
know yeah what are you saying I got
offered the head chef job at
alesandro's what it's okay cuz you know
what if you think about it you don't
really need me for the business you're
the cook
without you it's just me driving up to
people's houses with empty trays and
asking for
money all right but um well I I'll pay
you back all the money you invested and
you can keep the van for
what can't believe this got to get out
of here B wait a
minute I'm an assistant buyer
[Music]